## Hassan Hammoud

## Junior Full Stack Web Developer

**≥** hassanhammoud2000@gmail.com

+961-70 11 89 91

Akkar Governorate, Lebanon

github.com/Hassan-Hammoud

in linkedin.com/in/hassan-hammoud-3ha

I am a junior web developer with experience in full-stack development. I specialize in React and have a strong command of Node.js, MySQL, and MongoDB. I excel in fast-paced team environments and strive to deliver top-notch web solutions.

## **Experience**

Trainee, Codi Tech, full stack web developer

TRIPOLI 11/2022 - 05/2023

- A coding boot camp and a leadership course for six months, providing hands-on experience with real-life
  - Worked on full stack development projects for real client
  - $\circ~$  created, tested, and deployed dynamic web apps after gathering requirements.
  - Created innovative solutions in response to various clients' project requirements.
  - A cross-functional team and I worked together on all stages of the project development life cycle.

Media and content creation:

TRIPOLI 08/2022 - 10/2022

- Intensive course with Quad academy in partnership with Anera and Unicef:
  - Audience attraction
  - Script writing
  - Video editing
  - Photography basics
  - Adobe premiere basics
  - Content creation for different social media platform

## Education

Codi-Tech TRIPOLI 11/2022 - 05/2023

- Full stack web developer
  - Back end (Nodejs, PHP, SQL)
  - Front end (JavaScript, React, Bootstrap, Material.UI, Chart.JS)
  - Server Management (Lamp Stack, Linux)
  - Project Management (AGILE Methodology)
  - Content Management System (WordPress)

Institute Pedagogique national de l'enseignement technique (IPNET)

TRIPOLI 09/2020 - 05/2021

- Technical License in renewable energy
- GPA: 3.2

**Skills** 

- Programming
- Communication
- HTML5

- Wireframes
- Time Management
- CSS

- Github, Gitlab, Git
- Problem Solving
- JavaScript

- Adobe Premiere Pro
- Critical Thinking
- WordPress

Languages

- Arabic -> Native
- French -> Limited Working Proficiency
- English -> Limited Working Proficiency